Guide to the Harold Schmidt Collection ARS.0120
Archive of Recorded Sound
Harold Schmidt Collection
1940-1993
ARS.0120
12 boxes: 333 open reel tapes (13 10.5" reels; 276 7" reels; 41 5" reels; 3 3" reels); 40 audiocassettes; 2 video reels; 40 discs (2 10" instantaneous; 34 12" instantaneous; 4 custom pressings); one small box of slides and photographs
Archive of Recorded Sound
Sound recordings from Stanford University professor and choral director Harold C. Schmidt (1910-1993), including performances from the Stanford University Chorus, Choir, and Chamber Chorale.
Access
Open for research; material must be requested at least two business days in advance of intended use. Contact the Archive for assistance.
Source
The Harold Schmidt Collection was donated to the Stanford Archive of Recorded Sound by Carl Schmidt in 1994.
Scope and Contents
The Harold Schmidt Collection consists of sound recordings from Stanford University professor and choral director Harold C. Schmidt (1910-1993), including performances from the Stanford University Chorus, Choir, and Chamber Chorale. After graduating from Harvard, Schmidt studied with Walter Piston and Gustav Holst, and taught at Fisk University. In 1947, Schmidt joined Stanford as an associate professor. As director of the choir, he presided over nearly thirty years of commencements and Sunday services at Memorial Church before his retirement in 1975.
Schmidt programmed works by Berlioz, Brahms, Handel, Haydn, Mechem, Milhaud, Poulenc, and others, including many 16th and 17th century choral works he edited himself. Some recordings were used by Schmidt in his classes for demonstration and testing. Those tapes identified as lectures may contain the entire lecture or only the musical excerpts used. However some tapes are clearly of lectures by Schmidt, such as an intermission feature on KKHI's San Francisco Symphony broadcast (Schmidt established the Symphony's early morning open rehearsal series in 1972 and served as lecturer). The collection also includes rehearsals, auditions, pre-recorded electronic accompaniments, and worship services at Memorial Church, particularly from Christmas and Easter programs.
While not always identified, the principal performers are the Stanford University Chorus (whose name was later changed to Stanford University Symphonic Chorus), Stanford University Choir (later changed to Stanford Memorial Church Choir) and the Stanford Chamber Chorale. In most cases, Schmidt is conducting. Some recordings also feature contributions from professors Putnam Aldrich, Herbert Nanney, and Sandor Salgo, as well as the Stanford Symphony Orchestra. Highlights include the Stanford Summer Chorus performing the music of Randall Thompson, conducted by Thompson, Seiji Ozawa working with the University Chorus in 1970, the Chorus performing Lou Harrison’s La Koro Sutro from 1974 with Harrison directing, and the Memorial Church Choir performing a piece by Ligeti while he was a resident composer at Stanford.
The recordings are largely on open reel tape and cassette, but there are also a substantial number of instantaneous discs in the collection. Some recordings are indexed on a series of cards available at the Archive of Recorded Sound. Please note that identification here may not be correct; in many cases tapes appear to have been reused, and reels and boxes may have been shuffled. Additionally, handwriting is sometimes illegible, abbreviated, or conflicting. Many say "blank" or "erase" in addition to other information.
Related Collections
Other ARS collections that include Schmidt material include ARS0112, Stanford Tape Collection and ARS0116, Meyer Library Lecture Tapes. There are also instantaneous discs from Harold Schmidt in the Archive of Recorded Sound's Transcription Disc Collection: one 12" disc in box 12-811 and fourteen 16" discs in boxes 16-174,16-179, and 16-180.
Indexing Terms
Schmidt, Harold; Stanford University. Chamber Chorale.; Stanford University. Choir.; Stanford University. Chorus.; Choral music
- 1. Tapes, reel
  - Curt Allen, Tenor, 1969-06-20; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 7)
  - Curt Allen, Hymns From The Christian Science Hymnal, 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 10)
  - La Belle. Choruses. Reel 2, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Bach, Magnificat in D Major, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - Bach, Christmas Oratio, Archival Recording; Rameau; Stravinsky, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Bach, O Ewiges Feuer. New Tape, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Bach, O Ewiges. Aldrich, Choir and Chamber Orchestra, 1969-05-30; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 7)
  - Banchieri, Reel 2 [from box], 1964-08-07; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Leslie Bassett, Collect. Electronic Tape (World Library of Sacred Music TP-2084), 1970; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Beethoven, Op. 118, Chorale. Master, 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 7)
  - Beethoven, Op.68 No.6; Brahms, Concerto For Piano in Bb, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
  - Late Beethoven Choral Music. M. Tilson Thomas, Conductor. See Recording, Lecture, 1976-03-24; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Beethoven; Dvorak, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
  - Berlioz, L'Enfance, 1973-12-02; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Berlioz, Bizet, Beethoven. Open Rehearsal, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Brahms [?]; Schoenberg, Verklarte Nacht No.1; Reel II Mozart, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Brahms, Symphony No.2, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Brahms, Three Sonatas; CPE Bach, etc., 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Henry Brant, Solomon's Gardens, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Britten, Et Misericordum. 10-15, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - Bruckner, 6th Hillsborough, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - Cal Western University Chamber Singers and University Chorus. Christmas, 1964-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - Choral Music, Ash Wiley For Program [illeg], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Concert of Contemporary Choral Music, 1952-08-12; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 5, Audio 2)
  - Church Music Festival Celebrating Palo Alto's Diamond Anniversary. Memorial Church, 1969-04-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Corteccia; Festa, 1966-04-18; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
  - John Crawford, Magnificat. Nanney, Schmidt. Memorial Church, 1961-03-14; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Crown 712. Corteccia; Festa, 1966-03-17; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
  - Crown 712, 1966-03-19; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
  - DMQ Choral. 10 Examples, 1968-03-18; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Donizetti, Daughter Of The Regiment. Beverly Sills, Live TV Presentation, 1980; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Dumont, Magnificat, 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 7)
  - Dvorak, Stabat Mater; Mahler. April 9, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Felciano, Sic Transit, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - For All The Saints; Crucifixos I,II; We Praise The Sevenfold Amen; Tocata, Widor, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Sharon Furent [?] Interview [front of box]; Trovatore Feb. 6 '93 [back of box], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Gabrieli, In Ecclesiis. Nanney, Brass Ensemble, Schmidt. Memorial Church, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Glory To God In The Highest, 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 7)
  - Harrison Rehearsal, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
  - Lou Harrison, Mass, La Koro Sutro [probably University Chorus program from 11/17/74 with Harrison directing], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - Harvard Summer School Chorus, 1956-08-13; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 1)
  - Harvard Summer School Chorus, Schmidt, Director, 1957; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
  - Harvard Summer School Chorus. 2 of 2, 1957-08-01; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Harvard Summer School. Haydn, Lord Nelson Mass, 1960; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Joseph Haletky Audition Tape, Applying For DMA in Conducting, 1970-1971; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Haydn, Missa Pro Defuncto. Collegium Musicum of the University of Missouri, Minor, Conductor, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - Haydn, Symphony 102 Bb; Franck, Le Chasseur; Stravinsky, Sacre Du Printemps, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Haydn, Pinkham. Feb.6, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Hindemith, Op. 46 No.2, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - Hud Summer School, 3 7" open reel tapes (Audio 4, Audio 3)
  - Indiana University Women's Chorus, James A. Lucas, Conductor, 1967-11-15; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Ives 75, Symphony Excerpts, 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Jordan High School Choir, TD Ross, Director, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Kelterborn, Changements. SF Symphony, 1975-02-28; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Kodaly, Te Deum; Christmas Music (Carols), 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - [de Koven?,] Rob Roy. Sync Marela [?] 20-75, 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Kodaly; Poulenc; Niles; Zimmerman; Byrd; Handl. Sunday 440 1 and 2, 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 5)
  - KZSU, Opera, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - LA Tape: Excerpts of Stanford [illeg.], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Los Angeles Lyric Ensemble, Curt Allen, Director. Aspects of Love. First Presbyterian Church of Granada Hills [program enclosed], 1976-03-28; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Laudano di Cortona, Passione, Sgruzzi, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - Ligeti, SF Symphony, 1972-05; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 7)
  - Lindsay; Chesnikov [?]; Palestrina, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Madrigals, etc. Poulenc; Monteverdi; Copland; Milhaud, 1955-05-15; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Madrigals, Summer, 1951; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - Mahler, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Martinu, Madrigals, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Karl Marx, Three Cantatas for Chorale. Prof. Schmidt, Personal Tape., 1971-11-07; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Kirke Mechem, Singing Is A Good Thing, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - Mechem, Redid [illeg.] Song. Aldridge, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Kirke Mechem, The Victory of Zorobabel. Temple Choir, Elgin Choral Union. North Shore Congregation Israel, Glencoe, Ill., 1966-04-24; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - Mechem, O Sing unto the Lord. Jack Bertram, Trumpet. Thompson, Last Words of David. Schraeter Conducting, 1970-05-17; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - Milhaud, May 20 (M-t10 21), 1.0 10.5" open reel tape(s) (Audio 1)
  - Milhaud Program, 1953-03-01; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Milhaud Retake, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - Milhaud, Cantique Du Rhone, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
  - Milhaud, La Mort D'Un Tyran. Harvard Medical School Chorus and Instrumentalists, Kirchner, Conductor. Sanders Theatre. WHRB, 1965-12-16; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
  - Milhaud, La Tragedie Humaine. San Diego Symphonic Chorale, Directed by Milhaud, 1960-12-20; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Milhaud, Les Momies d'Egypte, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - Milhaud, Les Momies d'Egypte. Chorale, 1974-05-07; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - Milhaud, Trois Psaumes, 1967-06-06; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - Monteverdi, Magnificat. Promenade Concert, Royal Albert Hall, London. Accademia Monteverdiana Chorus and Orchestra, Denis Stevens, Conductor, 1970-08-18; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Mozart, Requiem, 1973-02-25; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
  - Mozart, Violin Concerto No.5 in D Major; Harris, Symphony No.3, 1 7" open reel tape folders (Audio 5)
  - Mozart; Schoenberg. Symphony April 4, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Ojai [illeg.]. Schmidt Evening Tuesday June 5. Henry Gibbons Things At End, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Operatic Miscellany and Trivia, 3 7" open reel tapes (Audio 4, Audio 5)
  - Orff, Camina Burana. Welling, SF Symphony, SF Symphony Chorus, SF Boys Chorus, 1981-05-20; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Orff, Catulli Carmina, Ludi Scaenici. Occidental College Glee Club, Howard Swan, Director [program enclosed], 1967-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Orff, Carmina Burana. LA Symphonic Chorus. Cerritos College Gymnasium [program enclosed], 1967-05-04; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 2)
  - Palestrina, Surge Amica Mia. Dubbed 1/17/62, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Pinkham, In The Beginning. Only Pre-recorded Tape, 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Daniel Pinkham, Jean Lunn. Mozart, Agnus Dei. Choir of King's Chapel 3/6/60; Mozart, Kommet her K146/317b. Cambridge Festival Orchestra 3/13/60, 1960-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Howard Pollack, Piano. SMRH, 1972-11-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Poulenc, La Voix Humaine, 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Poulenc, Litanies, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - [Puccini,] Madam Butterfly, Complete, 1981-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Puccini, Gianni Sebicchi, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
  - Rachmaninoff, Symphonic Dances, 1980-01-20; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
  - Rameau, Motet in Convertendo; Schoenberg, De Profundis (BBC Tape), 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Recorder Music Preceding Concert, 1967-12-10; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - R.T. Mass, 1955-05-15; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - RT Tape of 1963, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Leonard Rumery, Conductor. UCLA, 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 7)
  - Loren Rush, Excerpt From a Little Traveling Music, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - SF Symphony, De Waarts. Earl Brown, Cross-sections and Color Fields; FJ Haydn, Symphony No.8, 1977-03-04; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - SF Symphony, Keltenhorn, 1975-04; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - SF State Symphony, Lloyd Maes. Faure, 1970-05; 1 3" open reel tape (Audio 10)
  - Schmidt lectures
    - Los Altos Symphony Forum Lecture with Excerpts. Dec. 1, 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 2, Audio 5)
    - Total Lecture. Use for April 3, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
    - Elements Of Music. Sloan And Meyer, 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Excerpts for Mahler Lecture, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
    - Lecture 3/20/72; Lecture at Hillsboro 3/21/74, 1972-1974; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Professor Harold Schmidt, Intermission Feature on SF Symphony Broadcast, Taped at Open Rehearsal Briefing December 5. KKHI, 1973-12-07; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
    - Symphony Lecture, 1985-02-21; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Orff, Carmina Burana, Haydn Lecture, 1981-05-20; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
    - Beethoven, Eroica Eb. Complete Lecture, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Schmidt's May 10 Tape. Dedicated to Kent Students, 1970-05-10; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Schoenberg, De Profundis, BBC 11/62; Stockhausen, Momente, Cologne Radio 7/64; Smith, Two Motets, Bond Chapel Choir, University of Chicago 5/55, 1955-1964; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
  - Schumann, Scenes from Faust. Mt-7 211-212, 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 7)
  - Schutz; Weelkes; Monteverdi; Gesualdo, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - Ronald Sindelar, Medusa-The Ship. Pre-recorded Tape For Performance (Walton Music Corporation 31322), 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - [Sindelar,] Medusa - The Ship, 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Patricia Smith, Choral Conductor. L'Histoire, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Stanford Choir, Chorale performances (chronological)
    - undated
      - Part 1 of Christmas Mass. Hammerschmidt, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
      - Schmidt Christmas, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
      - Xmas Music? Chorus, Chorale. Poulenc; Burkhard; Cork; Pinkham; Pepping, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
      - Choir, Sundays, 69, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
      - University Summer Choir, Memorial Church. Reel 2,3 [program enclosed], 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 10)
      - Choral Concert, August 13. Holst, 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 6)
      - Stanford Choir. Bakersfield, Reel 1, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Beethoven, Ninth. SF Symphony, Krips, Stanford Chorus, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
    - Choral-3, 1951-11-27; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Candlelight Carol Service, Memorial Church, 1951-12-07; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
    - Stanford Chorus, Christmas Music, Art Gallery. M-t7 5. Use Over, 1953-12-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
    - Christmas Choral Program, Schmidt. Bender Room?, 1957-12-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
    - Buxtehude; Piston. Memorial Church, 1958-06-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
    - Freshman Chorus, 1958-1959; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
    - Choir, Christmas Church Services, 1959-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
    - Schutz, A German Requiem. Kopp, Conductor. University Choir, HCS Conducting, 1961-06-08; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
    - Palestrina. Choir, 1963-06-04; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Music of Randall Thompson, Conducted by the Composer. Stanford Summer Chorus, Schmidt. Dinkelspiel Auditorium. KXKX-FM, San Francisco [program enclosed], 1963-08-11; 10 open reel tapes: 2 10.5" reels; 7 7" reels; 1 5" reel (Audio 7, Audio 1, Audio 8)
    - University Chorus, Schmidt, Conductor. Dinkelspiel, 1963-11-17; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
    - Chorale, Museum. Christmas. 1 of 2, 1963-12-08; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
    - [Choir?] Marcello Psalm; Legnenzi. Reel 2. Stars, 1965-03-07; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Memorial Church Service [program enclosed], 1965-05-16; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
    - Stanford Choir, 1965-05-27; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Sacred Choral Concert. Haydn, Hymn to God. 1 of 2, 1965-07-21; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
    - Memorial Church Choir and Choral Workshop, Schmidt, Director. Nanney, Instrumental Ensemble. Memorial Church. Stanford Summer Festival [program enclosed], 1965-07-21; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 6, Audio 8)
    - Chorus. The Gate Of Heaven; Last Words of David, 1965-10-26; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 8)
    - Stanford University Chorus, Schmidt, Director. Dinkelspiel [program enclosed], 1965-12-03; 3 7" open reel tapes (Audio 6)
    - Service of Carols. Stanford Memorial Church, Christmas. KZSU, 1965-12-10; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 8)
    - Choir - Christmas, 1965-12-10; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Choir, Christmas Music, 1966-02-17; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Memorial Church Choir, KZSU, 1966-05-15; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Christmas Choral Music. Hammerschmidt, Alleluia, 1966-12; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Stanford Chorale, Stanford Wind Ensemble. Dinkelspiel, 1967-11-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Choir. Hammerschmidt, Zangius, 1967-12-08; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
    - Graduate Chorale Concert, 1967-12-10; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
    - 1/14-2/4. Bairstow; Haydn; Faure; Harris; Bach; Beethoven; Gibbons; Byrd, 1968; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - 2/25-3/17. Bach; Lassus; Faure; Holst; Kodaly; Scarlotti. Memorial Church Choir, 1968; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
    - 4/7-4/21. Faure; Gibbons; Vulpius; Lotti; Pinkham; Mendelssohn; Brahms, 1968-04; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
    - Palestrina, Missa Brevis. Memorial Church, 1968-04-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Choir, Public Worship Service. Haydn; Brahms [program enclosed], 1968-04-28; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - 5/5-6/2. Bloch; Blow; Hovhaness; Holst; Gibbons, 1968; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - Choir, Public Worship Service. Holst; Mozart [program enclosed], 1968-05-26; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - 5/19-9/22. Handel; Byrd; Schubert; Bach; Mendelssohn, 1968; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - 9/29-10/20. Mozart; Redford; Handel; Walton; Bairston, 1968; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - [Memorial Church Choir?] Hanson; Bloch, 1968-10-06; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - 10/27-11/10. Haydn; Lassus; Handel; Morley; Bach; Kastalsky, 1968; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - 11/17-11/24. Beethoven; Thomson; Bach; Holst, 1968; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - Choir, Christmas, 1968-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
    - [Ramirez,] Misa Criolla; Mechem. Tape 2, 4. Dinkelspiel, 1968-12-06; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 3)
    - Zimmerman; Byrd; Poulenc; Handl; Mechem; Handel, 1968-12-06; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - [Choir?] Kodaly; Niles; Poulenc, 1968-12-08; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
    - 1/12-1/26, 1969-01; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - 3/9-4/6. Handel; Bruckner; Mozart; Tallis; Vulpius; Lotti; Hammerschmidt, 1969; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - Founder's Day. Concert of Organ and Choral Music, Memorial Church [program enclosed], 1969-03-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - 4/13-5/11. Williams; Willan; Bach; Byrd; Mechem; Hovhaness; Mozart, 1969; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
    - 5/18-5/25. Bach, 1969-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
    - Sunday Choir. Bach; Weelkes; Haydn; Willan, 1969-06-01; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
    - 9/28-10/26. Bach; Williams; Holst; Hovahaness; Willan; Redford; Poulenc, 1969; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
    - Chorale, Sunday Afternoon Services, Dinkelspiel. Reel 2, 1969-11-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - Stanford Chorus and Chamber Orchestra, Salgo. Dinkelspiel Reel 3 [program enclosed], 1969-12-07; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - Christmas Service - Musical Parts, 1969-12-14; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
    - Messiah Christmas Concert Master, 1969-12-12; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 4, Audio 3)
    - Handel, Messiah From Lagunita, 1969-12-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - Chorale, Museum, 1969-12-14; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - Easter Sunday, Memorial Church. Harvard Glee Club, Elliot Forbes, Conductor [program enclosed], 1970-03-29; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Chorale, Memorial Church, 1970-06-01; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 2)
    - Chorus. Brahms; Mendelssohn; Willan. Baccalaureate, 1970-06-14; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
    - 10/25-11/8. Haydn; Morley; Poulenc; Bach; Ives, 1970; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
    - Bernstein, Chichester Psalms. Ozawa, Stanford Chorus Rehearsal, 1970-11-30; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
    - Haydn, Te Deum. Ozawa, Stanford Chorus Rehearsal, 1970-11-30; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - Choir, Carols. Christmas 12/6-12/13 [programs enclosed], 1970-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - Reading and Vesper by Zimmerman. Bernstein, Ending Chichester Psalm. Reel 2, 1970-12-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
    - Schmidt, Christmas Concert Reel 2 [program enclosed], 1970-12-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - Choir, Public Worship Service, Memorial Church 10/11/70-2/21/71 [programs enclosed], 1970-1971; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - Choir, Fall. Williams; Redford; Hanson; Morley; Mozart; Sweelinck; Holst; Dieterich; Clarke; Walton. Vivaldi; Williams; Bach; Nikolsky; Handel; Desprez, 1971; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 11)
    - Christmas Music From Stanford For KXRX, 1971; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Schmidt, Nanney. Program of Choral and Organ Music, Memorial Church [program enclosed], 1971-01-24; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 10)
    - Choir, Public Worship Service, Memorial Church. 1/10-1/31, 1971; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - Poulenc, Gloria. SF Symphony, Stanford, 1971-03-07; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Choir, Public Worship Service. 4/11-5/9 [program enclosed], 1971-05-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - Stanford Chorale, Sequoias, 1971-05-07; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
    - Choir, Public Worship Service. 5/16-5/23 [programs enclosed], 1971-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - Chorale. Mechem, Tails Out, Canons for Newlyweds [?], 1971-06-02; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
    - Stanford Chorale, Stanford Chamber Orchestra, Salgo, 1971-11-07; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - Stanford Choir, Schmidt, Director, 1971-12-10; 3 7" open reel tapes (Audio 8)
    - 12/5/71-1/30/72. Bach; Praetorius; Hawkins; Palestrina; Mozart; Hassler; Brahms; Thompson; Finzi, 1971-1972; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - University Chorus, Schmidt, Conductor [program enclosed], 1971-12-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
    - 2/6-3/12. Lotti; Tallis; Bassett; Byrd; Berlioz; Mozart; Hanson; Bloch, 1972; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)